[
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘ŠğŸ»ğŸ‘¨ğŸ»â€ğŸ¦²ğŸ¦¸ğŸ»â€â™‚ï¸",
        "response": "Ø³Ø§ÙŠØªÙ…Ø§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸâœğŸ»ğŸ““",
        "response": "Ù„Ø§ÙŠØª"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ«ğŸ§‘ğŸ»â€âš•ï¸â„ï¸ ",
        "response": "ØªØ´ÙˆØ¨Ø±"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ”¥ğŸ‘±ğŸ»â€â™‚ï¸â„ï¸ ",
        "response": "ØªÙˆØ¯ÙˆØ±ÙˆÙƒÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§‘â€ğŸ³ğŸ¦µğŸ»ğŸš¬",
        "response": "Ø³Ø§Ù†Ø¬ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ—âš”ï¸ğŸ‘¦ğŸ»",
        "response": "Ø§ÙŠÙ†ÙˆØ³ÙƒÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’€ğŸ¸ğŸ‘‘",
        "response": "Ø¨Ø±ÙˆÙƒ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ”¥ğŸ§‘ğŸ»â€ğŸš’ğŸš’",
        "response": "Ø´ÙŠÙ†Ø²Ø§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’‡ğŸ»â€â™€ï¸ğŸŒ¸ğŸ™ğŸ»â€â™€ï¸ ",
        "response": "Ø³Ø§ÙƒÙˆØ±Ø§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘¨ğŸ»â€ğŸ¦°ğŸœï¸ğŸº ",
        "response": "ØºØ§Ø±Ø§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¦ŠğŸœğŸ¥ ",
        "response": "Ù†Ø§Ø±ÙˆØªÙˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ€ğŸ“–ğŸ‘¿ ",
        "response": "Ø§Ø³ØªØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "â˜€ï¸ğŸ—¡ï¸ğŸ˜®â€ğŸ’¨",
        "response": "ÙŠÙˆØ±ÙŠØªØ´ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸğŸ˜›ğŸ”¬",
        "response": "Ø§ÙˆØ±ÙˆØªØ´ÙŠÙ…Ø§Ùˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "âš«âšªâ˜ï¸",
        "response": "Ø²ÙŠØªØ³Ùˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¤¡ğŸƒğŸ‘¦ğŸ»",
        "response": "Ù‡ÙŠØ³ÙˆÙƒØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§‘ğŸ»ğŸ”™ğŸ§‘",
        "response": "ØªØ§ÙƒÙŠÙ…ÙŠØªØ´ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘’ğŸ–ğŸ´â€â˜ ",
        "response": "Ù„ÙˆÙÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¥ªğŸ‘¦ğŸ»ğŸ‘ŠğŸ»",
        "response": "Ù…Ø§Ø´"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§›ğŸ»â€â™‚ï¸â˜€ï¸ğŸ‘¿",
        "response": "Ù…ÙˆØ²Ø§Ù†"
    },
    {
        "question": "â›“ï¸ğŸ‘€ğŸ§‘",
        "response": "ÙƒÙˆØ±Ø§Ø¨ÙŠÙƒØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ´â€â˜ ï¸âš“ï¸ğŸ¤¥ ",
        "response": "ÙŠÙˆØ³ÙˆØ¨"
    },
    {
        "question": "âš”ï¸ğŸŒŠğŸ§‘ğŸ»",
        "response": "ØºÙŠÙˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "âš”ï¸ğŸ”¥ğŸ§‘",
        "response": "Ø±ÙŠÙ†ØºÙˆÙƒÙˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "âš”ï¸ğŸ’¨ğŸ§‘ğŸ»",
        "response": "Ø³Ø§Ù†ÙŠÙ…ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "âš”ï¸ğŸ§‘ğŸ»â˜ï¸",
        "response": "ØªÙˆÙƒÙŠØªÙˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "âš”ï¸ğŸ‘©ğŸ»ğŸ¦‹ ",
        "response": "Ø´ÙŠÙ†ÙˆØ¨Ùˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "âš”ï¸ğŸ‘©ğŸ»ğŸ©· ",
        "response": "Ù…ÙŠØªØ³ÙˆØ±ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§‘ğŸ»ğŸª¨âš”ï¸",
        "response": "Ø¬ÙŠÙˆÙ…ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "âš”ï¸ğŸ§‘ğŸ»ğŸ‡ğŸ†",
        "response": "ØªÙŠÙ†ØºÙ†"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§‘ğŸ©ğŸ”¥",
        "response": "Ø³Ø§Ø¨Ùˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸœğŸ‘‘ğŸ’ªğŸ»",
        "response": "Ù…ÙŠØ±ÙŠÙˆÙ…"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ˜ˆğŸº",
        "response": "Ø¬ÙŠÙˆÙƒÙˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ­ ğŸ‘©ğŸ»ğŸ‘ï¸",
        "response": "Ø§Ù„ÙˆÙƒØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ˜ˆğŸ»ğŸ‘©ğŸ» ",
        "response": "Ù†Ø§ÙƒÙŠÙ…ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ˜ğŸ¥¶â„ï¸ğŸ‘ï¸",
        "response": "ØºÙˆØ¬Ùˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ˜ŠğŸ‘©ğŸ»ğŸ’°",
        "response": "Ù†Ø§Ù…ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’°â˜ ï¸ğŸ‘‘ğŸ´â€â˜ ï¸",
        "response": "Ø±ÙˆØ¬Ø±"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§‘â€ğŸ³ğŸ¦µğŸ»ğŸš¬",
        "response": "Ø³Ø§Ù†Ø¬ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘¦ğŸ»ğŸ›¹âš¡",
        "response": "ÙƒÙŠÙ„ÙˆØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸŒ™ğŸ¦‘ğŸ§‘ğŸ»â€ğŸ« ",
        "response": "ÙƒÙˆØ±Ùˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¸ğŸ»ğŸ” ",
        "response": "Ø¬ÙŠØ±Ø§ÙŠØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ€ğŸ“–ğŸ‘¿ ",
        "response": "Ø§Ø³ØªØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¤ğŸ¦‘âš”ï¸ ",
        "response": "ÙƒÙŠÙ„Ø± Ø¨ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ•µğŸ»â€â™‚ï¸ğŸ’ŠğŸ›¹ ",
        "response": "ÙƒÙˆÙ†Ø§Ù†"
}
]